Now let's put the spotlight on ICICI
Lombard. Yash joins in with the numbers.
Well, for ICICI Lombard in the fourth
quarter, it's a top-down beat from
premium growth to the underwriting
performance. As far as the gross written
premium is concerned, that saw a growth
of 17% on a year-on-year basis. The net
earned premium also saw a growth of 11%,
but more importantly, the number on the
net earned premium was 5790 crore, which
compares to a pool of 5731 crore. So, it
was much ahead of street estimates. As
far as the underwriting loss is
concerned, that came in at about 282
crore rupees versus 210 crore rupees. A
minor jump, but the street was
anticipating a number of close to about
350 crore rupees. So, much lower than
what the street was looking at as far as
underwriting loss is concerned.
Operating profit, the number came in at
about 546 crore rupees versus 571 crore
rupees. The street was only anticipating
a number of about 171 crore rupees. So,
much higher in terms of operating
profit. Finally, combined ratio, that
number came in at about 101.2
versus 102.5. So,
improvement of of about 100 basis points
on a year-on-year basis. The street was
expecting a number of 102.69.
So, it's an improvement from the levels
that the street was anticipating. Also,
a top-down beat for ICICI Lombard.
Okay, Yash. Thank you very much for
that.